<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Rekor</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Project Rekor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 08:12:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Run a Rekor Server</title>
      <link>/get_started/server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 08:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get_started/server/</guid>
      <description>Run a rekor server Create Database and populate tables Trillian requires a database, we use MariaDB for now (others to be explored later). Once this is installed on your machine edit the scripts/createdb.sh with your database root account credentials and run the script.
Build Trillian To run rekor you need to build trillian
go get github.com/google/trillian.git go build ./cmd/trillian_log_server go build ./cmd/trillian_log_signer Start the tlog server trillian_log_server -http_endpoint=localhost:8090 -rpc_endpoint=localhost:8091 --logtostderr .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client</title>
      <link>/get_started/client/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get_started/client/</guid>
      <description>Rekor Command Line Interface The following guide is targeted towards developers / software maintaieners who would like to make a release entry into the rekor transparency log.
The steps outlined below will show how to sign your software and then use the rekor CLI to make and verify an entry.
Download the Rekor CLI application  download details
Sign your release Before using rekor, you are required to sign your release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 17:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Seems like Rekor is centralised, is this true?  Yes, and why not? There is no need for a distributed source of transparency. There can be multiple sources of transparency and this only adds more sources of security guarantees, not less. An entity can post to as many logs as they want and inform users of where they post.  Why use a Merkle Tree / Transparency log?  Trillian is the back end technology used for certificate transparency Open source community with active development Deployed by Google, CloudFlare (nimbus), Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt Performance (Handles thousands of requests per second)  Why not use a blockchain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/get_started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get_started/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
